(Leonard:)Penny and I are throwing this
second wedding for your benefit.
(Leonard:)Can you please not ruin it?
(Alfred:)Of course. I'm sorry.
(Beverly:)Oh, look at that...
you can apologize.
Mom!
I'm sorry.
(Mary:)You know, the Bible
says forgiveness...
Mom!
I'm sorry.
(Penny:)Uh, who's hungry?
(Penny:)We have a reservation
at the best restaurant in town.
(Sheldon:)It only got three-and-a-half
stars on Yelp.
Sheldon!
I'm not sorry. That's true.
(Howard:)I don't know what to do.
(Howard:)It's the Air Force.
(Howard:)I mean, should I respond
to their e-mail?
(Howard:)Ignore it?
(Raj:)You can't ignore it.
(Raj:)It's not that postcard
that says it's time
(Raj:)to go back to the dentist.
(Bernadette:)Guys, come on.
(Bernadette:)We're meeting everyone
for dinner.
(Howard:)One sec. I'm just afraid
(Howard:)if I respond,
then they'll know I got it.
(Raj:)Oh, dude.
(Raj:)The minute you opened
that e-mail,
(Raj:)they knew you got it.
(Raj:)I mean, they're probably
looking at you
(Raj:)through the camera right now.
Oh, damn.
(Raj:)I love America.
(Bernadette:)Are you done with this nonsense?
(Howard:)It's not nonsense.
(Howard:)This is how the
U.S. military works.